Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 4 Locals, 2.
  - Local 425
    - Local 425 Factionalism and Grievances, June 29-October 18, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Officer Meeting Minutes, June 29, 1944; 1.
      - Ruth Young to Julius Emspak, July 12, 1944; 2.
      - Joseph Dermody Memo to Emspak, October 18, 1944; 3.
    - Local 425 Misappropriation, October 24-31, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Frederick Livingston to James McLeish with October 24, 1944, Albert Olsen Letter to Livingston, October 30, 1944; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to McLeish, October 31, 1944; 2.
    - Local 425 Wright Automatic Organization, June 3-9, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - James Matles to Henry Fiering, June 3, 1948; 1.
      - Fiering to Matles, June 9, 1948; 2.
    - Local 425 Correspondence and Wage Rates, January 1939-December 1947 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Notes Regarding United Instruments Workers, January 1939; 1.
      - John Carmody to UE Regarding Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers and Operating Engineers Inter-union Rivalry, August 2, 1941; 2.
      - James Listig to Julius Emspak Regarding Sperry Transfer, March 18, 1940; 3.
      - New York Journal Excerpt Regarding Ford Instrument Arbitration, December 8, 1947; 4.
      - Greetings, 5.
      - Ford Instrument Wage Rates, 6.
    - Local 425 Newspapers, February 1942-April 1944 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - The Chanticleer, February-May, 1942; 1-4.
      - The Range Keeper, April 1944; 5.
    - Local 425 Leaflets, October 27, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - "To All Employees of Sperry Gyroscope", October 27, 1938; 1.
      - "Ford Company Breaks Contract, Fires Shop Steward", 2.
      - "Mary Ellen Fired", 3.
      - "The Company is Busting Your Union", 4.
    - Local 425 Fourth Anniversary Pamphlet, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Local 425 Press Release, "Local 425 Repudiates Misleading Newspaper Articles", May 21, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Local 425 Newspaper Clippings, March 1, 1941-June 26, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - "CIO Instrument Makers Offer to Work 60 Hour Week for Navy," New York Times with May 19, 1941, Osgood Nichols Letter to James Carey, May 18, 1941; 1.
      - "The Case of 5300 vs. War Labor Board," New York Times, June 26, 1944; 2.
      - "Youth in Ford Instrument Mart Build Strong Unions," Challenge fo Youth, March 1, 1941; 3.
  - Local 426
    - Local 426 Constitution (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Local 426 Officers Lists, February 20, 1940-January 31, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Local 426 Officers Lists, December 28, 1951-January 26, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Local 426 Membership Resolution Regarding Standard Oil and Interessen-Gemeinschaft Farben with April 23, 1942, Arthur Davis Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, April 12, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Local 426 Incoming Correspondence, June 24, 1940-January 14, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Julius Emspak to Sidney Brooks Regarding Finances, June 24, 1940; 1.
      - Emspak to Brooks Regarding Mailing List, September 26-October 18, 1940; 2-3.
      - Emspak to Joseph Dunn Regarding White Collar Workers Organization, May 7, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Dunn Regarding Finances and UE News, May 14, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Authur Davis, October 21, 1941; 6.
      - Emspak to Davis Regarding Pittsburgh Trip, October 28, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak to Dunn Regarding Mailing List, January 7, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Davis Regarding Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Strike, February 16, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Jack Trugman Regarding Trial Factionalism, September 21, 1942; 10.
      - Emspak to Davis Regarding Brown-Wagner Resolution, September 24, 1942; 11.
      - Emspak to Davis Regarding Trugman Case and Factionalism, October 16, 1942; 12.
      - Emspak to Clayton Lang Regarding Trugman Case and Factionalism with December 15-16, 1942, General Executive Board Minutes Excerpt, Februray 26, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to Lang Regarding Finances, June 14, 1943; 14.
      - Emspak to Frank Hall Regarding Finances, July 19, 1944; 15.
      - Emspak to Dunn Regardng Veterans Dues, February 6, 1945; 16.
      - Emspak to Dunn Regarding Dues Check-off, October 22, 1946; 17.
      - Emspak to Dunn Regarding Finances, January 14, 1947; 18.
    - Local 426 Incoming Correspondence, January 15, 1942-March 30, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Julius Emspak to Charles Veneri Regarding Finances, March 20-April 10, 1950; 1-4.
      - Emspak to Maurice Veneri Regrading Finances, April 17-24, 1950; 5-6.
      - Emspak to Sam Boyd Regarding Finances, January 12, 1953; 7.
      - Emspak to Fred Nittoli Regarding Local 426 Dance, March 30, 1953; 8.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Arthur Davis Regarding Officers and Citizenship, January 15, 1942; 9.
      - Fitzgerald to Clayton Lang Regarding Membership Meeting, July 29, 1943; 10.
      - Fitzgerald to Nittoli Regarding Local 426 Dance, March 24, 1953; 11.
    - Local 426 Incoming Correspondence, Apri l29, 1941-April 16, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - James Matles to Arthur Davis Regarding Contracts, April 29, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Davis Regarding Political Action, May 2, 1941; 2.
      - Matles to Josephine Kielzenski Regarding Contracts, July 3, 1941; 3.
      - Matles to Davis Regarding Contracts, July 16, 1941; 4.
      - Matles to Kielzenski Regarding Staff Members, July 23, 1941; 5.
      - Matles to Kielzenski Regarding Westinghouse Conference, July 25, 1941; 6.
      - Matles to Kielzenski Regarding C.S. Jackson Case, August 6, 1941; 7.
      - Matles to Kielzenski Regarding Staff Members, August 13, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Davis Regarding Organization, August 25, 1941; 9.
      - Matles to Davis Regarding Fingerprinting, March 18, 1942; 10.
      - Matles to Clayton Lang Regarding Contracts, May 12, 1942; 11.
      - Matles to Davis Regarding Contracts, May 19, 1942; 12.
      - Matles to Kielzenski Regarding Local 426 Dance, January 7, 1943; 13.
      - Matles to Maurice Veneri Regarding Local 426 Dance, April 12, 1951; 14.
      - Matles to Fred Nittoli Regarding Local 426 Dance, March 27, 1953; 15.
      - Matles to Veneri Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 2, 1953; 16.
      - Matles to Veneri Regarding Finances, April 16, 1953; 17.
      - W.F. McNair to Al Strean Regarding Organization, February 19, 1947; 18.
      - David Scribner to Jack Trugman Regarding War Labor Board, January 26, 1945; 19.
      - Scribner to Veneri Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 1, 1953; 20.
    - Local 426 Outgoing Correspondence, June 1940-October 1943 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Maximalian Becker to James Matles Regarding Organization, August 1941; 1.
      - Sidney Brooks to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 1940; 2.
      - Arthur Davis to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 30, 1940; 3.
      - Davis to Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, July-December 1940; 4-5.
      - Davis to Emspak Regarding Strikes, February 11, 1941; 6.
      - Davis to Matles Regarding Grievances, April 11, 1941; 7.
      - Davis to T. Turner Regarding Grievances, April 11, 1941; 8.
      - Davis Telegram to Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, April 28, 1941; 9.
      - Davis to Matles Regarding Strikes, April 29, 1941; 10.
      - Davis to Canadian Department of Justice Regarding C.S. Jackson Case, July 16-21, 1941; 11-12.
      - Davis to Franklin Roosevelt Regarding C.S. Jackson Case, July 28, 1941; 13.
      - Davis to Emspak Regarding Constitution with Proposed Articles, October 11, 1943; 14.
      - Davis to Emspak Regarding Local 426 Dance with Two Tickets, October 17, 1941; 15.
      - Davis Telegram to Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, October 28, 1941; 16.
      - Davis to Abrams Regarding Finances with Two Airline Tickets, November 4, 1941; 17.
    - Local 426 Outgoing Correspondence, July 21, 1941-October 22, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Arthur Davis Telegram to James Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, November 14, 1941; 1.
      - Davis to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 426 Consitution, December 29, 1941; 2.
      - Davis to Jim Regarding Collective Bargaining, January 21, 1942; 3.
      - Davis to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference, February 3, 1942; 4.
      - Davis Telegram to Matles Regarding Collective Bargaining, February 11, 1942; 5.
      - Davis to Matles Regarding Contracts, February 12, 1942; 6.
      - Davis to Jim Regarding Wages and Job Classification, February 16, 1943; 7.
      - Davis to Stella Abrams Regarding Transfers, February 19, 1942; 8.
      - Davis to Julius Emspak Regarding Jack Trugman Case, October 15, 1942; 9.
      - Davis Telegram to Matles Regarding Contracts, July 30, 1942; 10.
      - Davis to Emspak Regarding Trugman Case and Factionalism, December 3, 1942; 11.
      - Davis to Jim Regarding Collective Bargaining, 12.
      - Joseph Dunn to UE Regarding Veterans Dues, February 1, 1945; 13.
      - Dunn to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, October 18, 1946; 14.
      - Frank Hall to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 22, 1952; 15.
      - Josephine Kielzenski to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference, July 21, 1941; 16.
      - Kielzenski to Matles Regarding C.S. Jackson Case with August 6, 1941, Matles Memo to Tom Wright and July 21, 1941, W. Stuart Edwards Letter to UE, July 28, 1941; 17.
      - Kielzenski to Matles Regarding Officers, August 11, 1941; 18.
    - Local 426 Outgoing Correspondence, January 20, 1942-March 21, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Clayton Lang to Mr. Turner Regarding Stewards Grievances, January 20, 1942; 1.
      - Lang Telegram to UE Regarding Collective Bargaining, August 10, 1942; 2.
      - Lang Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, September 23, 1942; 3.
      - Lang to UE Regarding Finances, June 7, 1943; 4.
      - Lang to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meetings, July 28, 1943; 5.
      - Fred Nittoli to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 426 Dance, March 21, 1953; 6.
      - Nittoli to James Matles Regarding Local 426 Dance, March 21, 1953; 7.
      - Nittoli to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 426 Dance, March 21, 1953; 8.
      - James Rocco to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 15, 1944; 9.
      - Maurice Veneri to Emspak Regarding Wages and Finances, August 18, 1948; 10.
      - Veneri to James McLeish Regarding 1951 UE Convention, September 19, 1951; 11.
      - Veniri to James McGranery Regarding Matles Case, November 19, 1952; 12.
      - Veniri to Matles Regarding Finances, May 1, 1953; 13.
      - Strike Committee Telegram to Matles Regarding Strikes, 14.
      - Rank and File Members Telegram to Matles, 15.
    - Local 426 Salary and Expense Letters, December 13, 1940-December 19, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Sidney Brooks, December 13-26, 1940; 1-2.
      - Joseph Dunn, Februray 3-December 19, 1941; 3-13.
    - Local 426 Checks, March 20-April 24, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Local 426 Check Photostat, June 22, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Local 426 White Collar Workers and Collective Bargaining, November 5-10, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Memo, November 5, 1941; 1.
      - Keysheet, 2.
      - Memo with Art Davis Letter to James Matles, November 10, 1941; 3.
    - Local 426 Jack Trugman Case Charges, June 19, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Local 426 Jack Trugman Case Hearing Transcript, June 22, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 27-32)
    - Local 426 Jack Trugman Case Roll Call, July 8, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Local 426 Jack Trugman Case, September 3-4, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Petition, September 3, 1942; 1.
      - Depositions, September 4, 1942; 2.
    - Local 426 Secession, July 15-December 17, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Draft Telegram, July 15, 1953; 1.
      - Bill Santora to Julius Emspak, October 21, 1953; 2.
      - Basil Pollitt Memo to James Matles, December 17, 1953; 3.
    - Local 426 Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, August 11, 1939-June 7, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Walter Mugford to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, August 11, 1939; 1.
      - Turner Conference Minutes with July 19, 1940, Peter Besch Letter to James Matles, July 11, 1940; 2.
      - Besch to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 15, 1940; 3.
      - Martha Schmitt to David Scribner Regarding War Labor Board, June 7, 1945; 4.
    - Local 426 Newspaper, 426, September 27, 1939-September 17, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Local 426 Leaflets, 1941-1949 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - "A Most Cordial Invitation" Regarding White Collar Workers, October 24, 1941; 1.
      - Dance and Revue, November 15, 1941; 2.
      - "Don't Forget the Meeting" Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, November 13, 1949; 3.
      - "Ed Brannangan" Regarding Local 426 Officers, 1949; 4.
      - "Local 426 Meets Management" Regarding Organization, 5.
  - Local 427
    - Local 427 Officers Lists, December 14, 1939-October 31, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Local 427 Incoming Correspondence, December 12, 1939-February 23, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Bill Chan to Matthew McDonald Regarding Newspaper, December 5, 1945; 1.
      - Cahn to Ernest Thompson Regarding UE Steward, May 23-June 27, 1949; 2-3.
      - Julius Emspak to Ben Mintz Regarding Bonding, December 12, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to Mary Vaivada Regarding Stamps, February 6, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Mary Krall Regarding UE Stamps, November 8-December 18, 1940; 6-7.
      - Emspak to Sol Potegal Regarding Constitution, December 30, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Krull Regarding UE News, April 1, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Krull Regarding Cornell Dubilier, April 19, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak to Potegal, November 11, 1942; 11.
      - Emspak to Potegal Regarding Security, November 27, 1942; 12.
      - Emspak to Cordelia Jennings, December 28, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to Judy Markevich Regarding Contracts, April 9, 1945; 14.
      - Emspak to Cliffton Cameron Regarding Amalgamation, June 13, 1945; 15.
      - Emspak to Mintz Regarding Per Capita, April 22, 1946; 16.
      - Emspak to Jennings Regarding UE News, September 16, 1946; 17.
      - Emspak to Sarah LaCava Regarding Withdrawal Card, November 1, 1948; 18.
      - Emspak to Thompson Regarding Finances, February 23-August 2, 1949; 19-21.
      - Emspak to Frederick Kolman Regarding Officers, August 19, 1949; 22.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Potegal with October 14, 1943, Dorothy Griffin Letter to Phillip Murray Regarding Initiation Fee, October 25, 1943; 23.
      - Fitzgerald to Cameron Regarding Amalgamated Local 427, June 13, 1945; 24.
      - Fitzgerald to Cameron, July 18, 1945; 25.
      - Fitzgerald to Tom Neill Regarding Officers, March 12, 1947; 26.
    - Local 427 Incoming Correspondence, February 2, 1940-April 27, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - James Matles to Sol Potegal Regarding Radio Advisory, February 2, 1940; 1.
      - Matles to S. Potegal Regarding Contracts, February 16, 1940; 2.
      - Matles to S. Potegal Regarding Federal Labor Union and Cornell-Dubilier, March 5, 1940; 3.
      - Matles to S. Potegal Regarding Federal Labor Union, April 11, 1940; 4.
      - Matles to Regina O'Brien, June 1, 1940; 5.
      - Matles to S. Potegal, April 4, 1942; 6.
      - Matles to S. Potegal Regarding Finances, May 4, 1942; 7.
      - Matles to S. Potegal Regarding Bubrock Wilcox, July 6, 1942; 8.
      - Matles to S. Potegal Regarding Contracts, December 8, 1942; 9.
      - Matles to S. Potegal, March 22, 1943; 10.
      - Matles to Leo Potegal Regarding Finances, September 7, 1943; 11.
      - Matles to Sadie Rosenberg, February 5, 1947; 12.
      - Matles to Ernest Thompson, March 25, 1948; 13.
      - Matles to Edward Lopez Regarding Organization, April 27, 1948; 14.
      - Russ Nixon to James Duffy Regarding Political Action Committee, November 3, 1947; 15.
      - R.N. Towsen to S. Potegal Regarding Dismissal and Compensation, December 10, 1943; 16.
    - Local 427 Outgoing Correspondence, May 27, 1940-August 16, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Clifton Cameron to Julius Emspak Regarding Negotiations with Cameron Letter to Roy Broughton Regarding Office of Price Administration, March 6, 1946; 1.
      - Cameron to James Matles Regarding Organization, May 31, 1946; 2.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation, June 11, 1945; 3.
      - Cameron to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Amalgamation, June 12, 1945; 4.
      - Cameron to Fitzgerald, July 12, 1945; 5.
      - Cameron to Emspak Regarding Electro-Dynamic Works, July 30, 1945; 6.
      - Cameron to Winchard Dee Regarding General Electric Organization, June 6, 1946; 7.
      - James Duffy to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 2, 1947; 8.
      - Duffy to Tom Wright, December 16, 1947; 9.
      - Dorothy Griffin to Phillip Murray Regarding Initiation Fee, October 27, 1943; 10.
      - Cordelia Jennings Letter Regarding Local 427 Records, December 23, 1943; 11.
      - Jennings to UE Regarding Finances, April 16, 1943; 12.
      - Jennings to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, September 20, 1946; 13.
      - Frederick Kosman to Murrary Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 29, 1948; 14.
      - Kosman to Emspak Regarding Local 427 Electro-Dynamic Works Strike, July 19, 1948; 15.
      - Kosman to Matles Regarding Officers, March 22, 1949; 16.
      - Kosman to Emspak Regarding Electro-Dynamics Inter-union Rivalry, August 16, 1949; 17.
      - Sarah LaCava to UE Regarding Transfer Card, October 29, 1948; 18.
      - Edward Lopez to Matles, May 27, 1940; 19.
      - Lopez to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, May 26-August 10, 1941; 20-22.
      - Lopez to Matles Regarding UE Convention, January 2, 1942; 23.
      - Lopez to Matles Regarding Organization, April 16, 1948; 24.
    - Local 427 Outgoing Correspondence, Decembe 2, 1939-July 27, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Ben Mintz to James McLeish Regarding Finances, September 14, 1945; 1.
      - Tom Neil to Albert Fitzgerald, March 7, 1947; 2.
      - Neil to Ben Riskin, March 20, 1947; 3.
      - Regina O'Brien to UE Regarding Bonding, December 2, 1939; 4.
      - O'Brien to UE Regarding Local 427 Constitution, January 17, 1940; 5.
      - Joseph Parente to Walter Barry Regarding Factionalism with "A Sincrere Unionist" Letter to UE Regarding Local 427, December 19, 1944; 6.
      - Sol Potegal to James Matles Regarding Organization, February 27, 1940; 7.
      - Potegal to Matles Regarding Solar Manufacturing, July 8, 1940; 8.
      - Potegal to Matles, October 13, 1941-April 1, 1942; 9-10.
      - Potegal to Matles Regarding Labor Advisory Committee, April 28, 1942; 11.
      - Potegal to Matles Regarding Babroch and Wilcox, July 1, 1942; 12.
      - Potegal to Matles Regarding Security Questionnaire, November 9, 1942; 13.
      - Potegal to Julius Emspak Regarding Security Questionnaire with October 7, 1942, Letter from WIlliam Mollow and "Personnel Security Questionnaire", November 10, 1942; 14.
      - Potegal to UE, November 30, 1942; 15.
      - Potegal to Matles Regarding Solar Manufacturing Company, December 2, 1942; 16.
      - Potegal to Matles, June 11, 1943; 17.
      - Ernest Thompson to Emspak Regarding Contract, July 15, 1947; 18.
      - Thompson to David Ranter Regarding Insurance, December 9, 1947; 19.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 4, 1949; 20.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 15-July 27, 1949; 21-23.
      - Mary Vaivada to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 5, 1940; 24.
      - Dolores Wepner to Ratner Regarding Bonding, January 27, 1949; 25.
    - Local 427 Finances, January 9, 1940-December 3, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Bonding Form, January 9, 1940; 1.
      - Expense Form, September 7, 1943; 2.
      - Ledger, July 30, 1947; 3.
      - Per Capita and Supply Payment Form with November 15, 1949, Paramound & Metal Spinning and Stamping Company Letter to UE Regarding Dues and Check-off, December 3, 1949; 4.
    - Local 427 Salary and Expense Letters To Mary Krull, July 28-August 22, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Local 427 International Nickel Strike, December 11-26, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, December 11, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to James McLeish, December 14, 1945; 2.
      - McLeish to Emspak, December 26, 1945; 3.
    - Local 427 Electric Boat Strike, May 1-July 13, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Report of Strike, May 1, 1948; 1.
      - Termination of Strike, June 10, 1948; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Thomas Provost, July 13, 1948; 3.
    - Local 427 Correspondence and Notifications of Pending Disagreements, May 20, 1942-April 30, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Russ Nixon to James McLeish Regarding Solar Manufacturing and Wages, May 20, 1942; 1.
      - Nixon to Nathan Cowen Regarding Political Action, May 20, 1942; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to McLeish Regarding Community Chest, Februray 25, 1943; 3.
      - Dorothy Griffin Letter Regarding Solar Manufacturing with October 22, 1943, Mercedes Daugherty Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, October 14, 1943; 4.
      - Julius Emspak to M.E. Hall Regarding Electric Boat, August 14, 1945; 5.
      - David Scribner to Ernest Thompson Regarding Local 442, December 7, 1945; 6.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Local 427 Bergen Point Iron Works Strike, August 16, 1946; 7.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Keuffel Esser and Local 427, October 10, 1946; 8.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Local 427 Electro-Dynamics Strike, March 12, 1947; 9.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Local 427 Hoegger Strike, March 12, 1947; 10.
      - David Scribner to James Matles Regarding Local 427 American Radiator Collective Bargaining, April 30, 1947; 11.
      - Helen Memo to Matles Regarding Solar Manufacturing Wages, 12.
  - Local 428
    - Local 428 Officers Lists, May 22, 1942-September 10, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Local 428 Membership Lists, September 30, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Local 428 Incoming Correspondence, September 28, 1942-May 2, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Julius Emspak to Constance Mack Regarding Bonding, September 28, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Constance Pappalardo Regarding Officers, May 1, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Margaret Gibbons, August 28, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Frank Cmero Regarding White Plains General Electric Charters, March 30, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to Paul Kubitz Regarding Initiation Fee, May 3, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Pat Barile Regarding Per Capita, November 27, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to Barile Regarding Finances, September 12, 1949-February 8, 1950; 7-8.
      - Emspak to Margaret Sheppard Regarding Per Capita, January 15, 1951; 9.
      - Emspak to Barile Regarding Local 428 Sonotone Strike, September 7, 1955; 10.
      - Emspak to Barile Regarding Per Capita, November 18, 1955; 11.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Barile, March 4, 1947; 12.
      - Fitzgerald to Fred Smith, March 4, 1947; 13.
      - Fitzgerald to Agnes Murphy, June 18, 1947; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Barile Regarding Sonotone Corporation Strike, August 16, 1955; 15.
      - James Matles to Barile Regarding Finances, October 16, 1947, September 21, 1955; 16-17.
      - Matles to Barile Regarding Westinghouse Strike, May 2, 1956; 18.
      - Russ Nixon to Barile Regarding Political Action Committee, November 6, 1947; 19.
      - Grant Reeves to Local 428 Regarding Dues Increase, December 30, 1950; 20.
      - Irving Schachtel to Max Drechman Regarding Executive Order Number 9240, November 25, 1942; 21.
      - David Scribner to Cmero Regarding Foreman Organization, May 29, 1945; 22.
      - C.F. Walsh to Barile Regarding Union Representitive, June 15, 1949; 23.
    - Local 428 Outgoing Correspondence, August 16, 1943-June 19, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Pat Barile to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 25, 1946; 1.
      - Barile to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, June 20, 1947; 2.